<?xml version="1.0"?>
<nguyejea>
	<title>Jeanice's Assignment 2</title>
	
	<student program = "Software Development and Network Engineering">
	</student>

	<student studentNumber = "991397535">
	</student>

	<movie image = "images/moana.jpg">
		<movieName>Moana</movieName>
		<plot>In Ancient Polynesia, when a terrible curse incurred by the Demigod Maui reaches an impetuous Chieftain's daughter's island, she answers the Ocean's call to seek out the Demigod to set things right.</plot>
		<cast>
			<actor name = "Auli'i Cravalho">
				<role>Moana</role>
			</actor>
			<actor name = "Dwayne Johnson">
				<role>Maui</role>
			</actor>
			<actor name = "Rachel House">
				<role>Gramma Tala</role>
			</actor>
		</cast>
		<reviews>
			<review>The narrative is a fairly predictable hero's journey -- Maui even calls her "The Chosen One" -- but the movie is refreshing for its lack of a love interest; instead Moana learns how to chart her own course.</review>
			<review>An absolute delight, a lush, exuberant quest fable full of big musical numbers and featuring perhaps the most stunning visuals of any Disney film to date.</review>
			<review>The film achieves what the best Disney animated features do: a sense of place that is refined and specific.</review>
		</reviews>
	</movie>

	<movie image = "images/zootopia.jpg">
		<movieName>Zootopia</movieName>
		<plot>In a city of anthropomorphic animals, a rookie bunny cop and a cynical con artist fox must work together to uncover a conspiracy.</plot>
		<cast>
			<actor name = "Ginnifer Goodwin">
				<role>Judy Hopps</role>
			</actor>
			<actor name = "Jason Bateman">
				<role>Nick Wilde</role>
			</actor>
			<actor name = "Idris Elba">
				<role>Chief Bogo</role>
			</actor>
		</cast>
		<reviews>
			<review>Zootopia excels on so many levels that it stands with the finest of the Disney classics.</review>
			<review>There's a lot here for kids to like and nearly as much to keep parents from fidgeting.</review>
			<review>What saves this big-budget cartoon behemoth is its modest, old-fashioned storytelling.</review>
		</reviews>
	</movie>

	<movie image = "images/findingdory.jpg">
		<movieName>Finding Dory</movieName>
		<plot>The friendly but forgetful blue tang fish, Dory, begins a search for her long-lost parents, and everyone learns a few things about the real meaning of family along the way.</plot>
		<cast>
			<actor name = "Ellen DeGeneres">
				<role>Dory</role>
			</actor>
			<actor name = "Albert Brooks">
				<role>Marlin</role>
			</actor>
			<actor name = "Ed O'Neill">
				<role>Hank</role>
			</actor>
		</cast>
		<reviews>
			<review>The film's number of memorable new characters are enough to mask its story problems.</review>
			<review>Finding Dory is, hands down, one of Pixar's best pieces of work to date and is nothing short of perfection.</review>
			<review>While not as visually dazzling as its predecessor, the film is still colorful and immersive; the script, while predictable, puts an engaging spin on the issues of home and identity.</review>
		</reviews>
	</movie>

</nguyejea>